{
    "subject": "resource/Antony_Thachuparambil",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:People_from_Kerala",
    "human_readable": "Antony Thachuparambil is a subject of Category:People from Kerala.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9550407528877258,
            "question": "Is Antony Thachuparambil a well-known person from Kerala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8219761252403259,
            "question": "What category does Antony Thachuparambil belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7549732327461243,
            "question": "Where is Antony Thachuparambil from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5551436543464661,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of people from Kerala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5541694164276123,
            "question": "Are there other notable individuals from Kerala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5031511187553406,
            "question": "What makes someone considered a 'person from Kerala'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4971979260444641,
            "question": "Can you tell me about people from Kerala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29993993043899536,
            "question": "What is Kerala known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20557330548763275,
            "question": "Are there any cultural events or traditions associated with Kerala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1714523285627365,
            "question": "What is the history of Kerala?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Antony Thachuparambil is a subject of Category:People from Kerala.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2068_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any cultural events or traditions associated with Kerala?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2068_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Kerala known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2068_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about people from Kerala?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2068_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2068_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation:\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is: \"Antony Thachuparambil is a subject of Category:People from Kerala.\"\n\nUpon reviewing the documents, I found that Antony Thachuparambil is mentioned as being born in Chalakudy, Thrissur Archdiocese (document 1) and Kottat, a suburban village of Chalakudy in Kerala to Poulose and Rosa (document 2). Additionally, his date of birth is given as December 8, 1894, which further supports the connection to Kerala.\n\nTherefore, the evaluation result is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Antony Thachuparambil, including his place of birth in Chalakudy, Thrissur District, Kerala, India. This supports the categorization of Antony Thachuparambil as a person from Kerala."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}